A Guide to the Letters to Oliver Evans, 1963-1972
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Letters to Oliver Evans, 1963-1972
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9917-a
This collection contains 35 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was purchased by the Library from Gotham Book Mart and Gallery, Inc., New York, New York, on November 20, 1973.
Scope and Content Information
Bowles discusses his autobiography and other writing projects of Evans and himself. He frequently mentions mutual acquaintances, particularly Carson McCullers, Tennessee Williams, Peter Owen, Gore Vidal, and Mohammed Mrabet. Many of the letters refer to an interview with Bowles done by Evans. The health of his wife Jane, life in Tangier, and travels of both of them are frequent topics.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Letters
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1963 October 18, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1963 December 19, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1964 January 13, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1964 February 11, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1964 May 11, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1964 July 14, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1964 August 2, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1964 October 27, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1964 December 22, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1965 January 15, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1965 April 22, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1965 April 22, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1965 June 7, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1965 September 22, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1965 October 18, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1968 June 12, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1968 August 1, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1969 February 7, ALS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1969 March 2, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1969 March 27, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1969 April 15, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1969 June 7, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1969 July 5, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1969 September 21, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1970 January 1, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1970 February 20, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1970 June 9, ALS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1970 June 24, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1970 July 4, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1970 October 26, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1971 January 26, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1971 April 20, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1972 March 19, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans 1972 June 10, TLS
  - Paul Bowles to Oliver Evans Wednesday, TLS
- 27 Envelopes 1968-1972